http://www.internet-radio.org.uk/terms/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We ask that you read this website privacy policy carefully as it contains important information on who we are, how and why we collect, store, use and share personal information, your rights in relation to your personal information and on how to contact us and supervisory authorities in the event you have a complaint.
This website privacy policy is divided into the following sections:
Who we are
Our website
Our collection and use of your personal information
Who we share your information with
Transfer of your information out of the EEA
Cookies and similar technologies
Marketing
Your rights
Keeping your personal information secure
How to complain
Changes to this website privacy policy
How to contact us
Who we are
This website is operated by Internet Radio Ltd. We are a limited company registered under company number 11756412 in England and Wales. We collect, use and are responsible for certain personal information about you. When we do so we are regulated under the General Data Protection Regulation which applies across the European Union (including in the United Kingdom) and we are responsible as ‘controller’ of that personal information for the purposes of those laws.
Our website
This privacy policy relates to your use of our website, internet-radio.com .
Throughout our website we may link to other websites owned and operated by advertisers. These other third party websites may also gather information about you in accordance with their own separate privacy polices. For privacy information relating to these other third party websites, please consult their privacy policies as appropriate.
Our collection and use of your personal information
We have set out below a description of all the ways we plan to use your personal data, and which of the legal bases we rely on to do so. The key below the table provides more information about the legal basis for processing your data. Where applicable we have identified what our legitimate interests are in relation to the processing of your data.
When information is collected
What information we collect
How and why we use your information
When you register with us as a user
Email address; IP address
We collect this:
to create and manage your account with us
to communicate with you about your account
We will keep this information until 6 months after you close your account with us we close your account
Legal Basis: contract; legitimate interests.
When you register with us as a broadcaster
Email address; IP address; responses to registration questions; details of your radio stations; payment information.
We collect this:
to create and manage your account with us
to take payment for any services you order
to communicate with you about your account
to address any queries or complaints regarding the content you stream using our service
We will keep this information until 6 months after you close your account with us we close your account
Legal Basis: contract; legitimate interests.
When you visit our site
When someone visits our site we collect standard web log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We also collect information from cookies (see our Cookie Policy for more details)
We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. We collect this information in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website using the data in the logs. We will not associate any log data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source.
It does not contain any personal data, therefore we do not need to establish a legal basis for processing it.
When you listen to radio station using our site
IP address
We use your IP address to display city-based location data regarding the location of that IP address.
When you leave a comment on our site, or contact us with an enquiry.
User name; comment content; IP address
We use this to post your comment on our website, or to address your question or comment about us or our service. We may also use it to improve our service and our website, encourage visitor feedback and discussion on our website.
We will keep this information until 6 months after you close your account with us we close your account
Legal Basis: consent; contract; legitimate interests.
The legal bases we may rely on include:
consent: where you have given us clear consent for us to process your personal information for a specific purpose
contract: where our use of your personal information is necessary for a contract we have with you, or because you have asked us to take specific steps before entering into a contract
legal obligation: where our use of your personal information is necessary for us to comply with the law (not including contractual obligations)
legitimate interests: where our use of your personal information is necessary for our legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of a third party (unless there is a good reason to protect your personal information which overrides our legitimate interests). These include our legitimate interests of us and our users in our providing a useful and high-functioning internet radio streaming service, and .
Who we share your personal information with
If you are a broadcaster, we may share your information with any person who notifies us of a complaint regarding infringement of rights or unlawful activity in your content.
We share your email address and username with our email service provider, Google Suite and Amazon SES. If you are a broadcaster, our payment service provider, Stripe will collect your payment information for the purposes of processing your payments for the service.
Some of those third party recipients may be based outside the European Economic Area — for further information including on how we safeguard your personal data when this occurs, see Transfer of your information out of the EEA.
We will share personal information with law enforcement or other authorities if required by applicable law, or (if you are a broadcaster) with any rights holders making complaints in respect of infringement of intellectual property or other rights infringed by your content.
Transfer of your information out of the EEA
We may transfer your personal information to the following which are located outside the European Economic Area (EEA) as follows:
Stripe processes your payment data in the USA so that it can can process your payment
The USA does not have the same data protection laws as the United Kingdom and EEA. Whilst the European Commission has not given a formal decision that such countries provide an adequate level of data protection similar to those which apply in the United Kingdom and EEA, any transfer of your personal information will be subject to appropriate safeguards as permitted the General Data Protection Regulation that are designed to help safeguard your privacy rights and give you remedies in the unlikely event of a misuse of your personal information. Stripe is certified under the EU-US Privacy Shield scheme;
see here for further details
Cookies and similar technologies
A cookie is a small text file which is placed onto your device when you use our website. We use cookies on our website. These help us recognise you and your device and store some information about your preferences or past actions.
For further information on our use of cookies, please see our Cookie Policy.
For further information on cookies generally visit www.aboutcookies.org; or www.allaboutcookies.org.
Marketing
We would like to send you information about our services, which may be of interest to you. Where we have your consent or it is in our legitimate interests to do so, we may do this by post, email, telephone, text message (SMS) or automated call.
We will only ask whether you would like us to send you marketing messages when you tick the relevant boxes when you provide your email address.
If you have previously agreed to being contacted in this way, you can unsubscribe at any time by:
contacting us at privacy@internet-radio.com
using the ‘unsubscribe’ link in emails or ‘STOP’ number in texts
For more information on your rights in relation to marketing, see Your rights below.
Your rights
Under the General Data Protection Regulation you have a number of important rights free of charge. In summary, those include rights to:
access to your personal information and to certain other supplementary information that this Privacy Notice is already designed to address
require us to correct any mistakes in your information which we hold
require the erasure of personal information concerning you in certain situations
receive the personal information concerning you which you have provided to us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit those data to a third party in certain situations
object at any time to processing of personal information concerning you for direct marketing
object to decisions being taken by automated means which produce legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affect you
object in certain other situations to our continued processing of your personal information
otherwise restrict our processing of your personal information in certain circumstances
For further information on each of those rights, including the circumstances in which they apply, see the Guidance from the UK Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) on individuals rights under the General Data Protection Regulation.
If you would like to exercise any of those rights, please:
email us at privacy@internet-radio.com
let us have enough information to identify you,
if we ask for it, let us have proof of your identity and address, and
let us know the information to which your request relates.
Keeping your personal information secure
We have appropriate security measures in place to prevent personal information from being accidentally lost, or used or accessed in an unauthorised way. We limit access to your personal information to those who have a genuine business need to know it. Those processing your information will do so only in an authorised manner and are subject to a duty of confidentiality.
We also have procedures in place to deal with any suspected data security breach. We will notify you and any applicable regulator of a suspected data security breach where we are legally required to do so.
If you want detailed information from Get Safe Online on how to protect your information and your computers and devices against fraud, identity theft, viruses and many other online problems, please visit www.getsafeonline.org. Get Safe Online is supported by HM Government and leading businesses.
How to complain
We hope that we can resolve any query or concern you raise about our use of your information.
The General Data Protection Regulation also gives you right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the European Union (or European Economic Area) state where you work, normally live or where any alleged infringement of data protection laws occurred. The supervisory authority in the UK is the Information Commissioner who may be contacted at https://ico.org.uk/concerns/ or telephone: 0303 123 1113.
Changes to this website privacy policy
This website privacy policy was last updated on 19th February 2019.
We may change this website privacy policy from time to time, when we do we will inform you via email, where appropriate.
How to contact us
Please contact us at privacy@internet-radio.com if you have any questions about this privacy notice or the information we hold about you.
